{
  "task": [
    {
      "question": " Who was Eve's first child?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Cain"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Abel"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Enoch"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Seth"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Cain",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " What was Cain's profession?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Shepherd "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Tailor"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Hunter "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Tiller "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Tiller ",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " Which of these were NOT part of God's curse on Cain?   ",
      "time": "15000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. He would have poor harvests all his life "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. He would be separated from the Lord"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. His first-born son and those of his descendants would all be born malformed"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. He would be a wanderer for life"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. His first-born son and those of his descendants would all be born malformed",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " What Cain offered as a sacrifice to God?    ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Vegetable of the soil"
        },
        {
          "choice": " Sheep"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Goat"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Fruit of the Soil"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Fruit of the Soil",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " Because Cain murdered Abel, the Lord curses him to a life as a?",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Vagabond"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Leper"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Beggar "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Hermit "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Vagabond",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " How did God say He knew what Cain had done? ",
      "time": "15000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Lucifer told the Lord what Cain had done"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Adam told Him"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. He was watching Cain from behind a bush"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Abel's blood cried to the Lord from the ground"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "d. Abel's blood cried to the Lord from the ground",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " The Lord declared that if Cain were to be killed: ",
      "time": "15000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Cain's murderer would be hunted as Cain was hunted "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b Cain's murderer would be sentenced to the same punishment"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Cain would be avenged seven times over "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. The entire family of Cain's murderer would be killed "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "c. Cain would be avenged seven times over ",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " How was Cain's punishment that is similar to the punishment of his parents, Adam and Eve? ",
      "time": "12000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. He was separated from God"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. He gained more knowledge"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. God hated him from then on"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. God would send Cain to hell"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. He was separated from God",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " Cain built a city and named it after his son. What was the name of this city?  ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Lamech"
        },
        {
          "choice": "b. Enoch"
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Irad"
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Mehujael"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "b. Enoch",
      "type": "epi_3"
    },
    {
      "question": " Where did Cain dwell after being cast out by the Lord? ",
      "time": "8000",
      "choices": [
        {
          "choice": "a. Nod "
        },
        {
          "choice": "b Sodom "
        },
        {
          "choice": "c. Gomorrah "
        },
        {
          "choice": "d. Eden "
        }
      ],
      "answer": "a. Nod ",
      "type": "epi_3"
    }
  ]
}